作曲 : TeddyLoid
作词 : TeddyLoid
编曲 : TeddyLoid
制作人 : TeddyLoid
Tell me what you need baby yeah
告诉我你想要什么，宝贝
Satisfaction’s what I get addicted
满足感使我上瘾
So affected
深受影响
And go round round round...
因此旋转，缠绕，涌动
As days go on, I thought that I won’t risk it
日渐星移，我以为我不愿再冒险
But I’m ready so steady, now now now now
但我已做好准备，此时此刻
Hop out to set us free from traps
跳跃起来，让我们摆脱陷阱
Yeah
是的
Come feel it, make it real and true oh
来感受，更真实的感受
Ooh
哦
I know you’re up to something new
我知道，你正在感受新奇
Let me show you, so hold on
让我袒露给你，所以，坚持住
I’ve got this right now
我现在就要得到
Off with the chains now
现在解开束缚
Di-lat-tat, Di-lat-tat
逐渐膨胀，不断放大
Change of a heart for tonight
今晚改变心意
Di-lat-tat, Di-lat-tat
逐渐膨胀，不断放大
Give me that, give me that bass
给我，给我那低吟
Give me that, give me that ace
给我，给我那招数
My sweet escape with you
亲爱的，我们一起逃离
Let’s go
来吧
Ah, Play back, play back...
啊，重播，回放
I’ve got a better feeling
我有更美妙的感受
Ah, Play back, play back...
啊，重播，回放
So take my hand, it’s for you
抓住我的手，它是你的
We could fly and runaway
我们可以飞奔着逃脱
Tell my heart to stay beating, beating
让我的心继续跳动，跳动
Wo-wo-wo-woah
喔 喔 喔 喔
Stay, stay, stay
继续，逗留，坚持
Wake up and find me you’ll see it
醒来后寻找我，你会明白的
And I’m just tired of finding all meanings
我疲于寻找所有的意义
So I’ll just take us, you won’t need a reason
就让我引导我们，你不需要任何理由
Come taste the flavor, flavor
品尝这鲜美，滋味
Play back, play back
重播，回放
Better late than never, now breathe in
迟到总比没有更好，现在深呼吸
Hear the time tick
听时间滴答作响
Ringing loud, loud, loud
铃声作响，作响，作响
And my hands are filled up with desire
我的双手溢满欲望
See it fall, make a vow
看它坠落，许下誓言
So we drown, drown, drown, drown...
让我们沉溺，沉溺，沉溺，沉溺
Reason to walk on my way
前行的原因
Gotta keep it sound cause I’ll stay
记得保持理智，因为我会继续
Let it go with the flow?
顺其自然吗
Listen up, get a will, open up
听话，遵从意愿，打开
Let them hear what you say
让他们听见你说的话
So keep it together till dawn
所以要坚持到天亮
Choices to make what we say
做出我们所说的选择
Living a life every day
享受现在
Why won’t you seek?
为什么你不寻找
Why don’t you see?
为什么你不明白
My only reason to keep on the show
我继续表演的唯一理由
Off with the hook now
别再被引诱
Di-lat-tat, Di-lat-tat
逐渐膨胀，不断放大
Once in a blue moon tonight
这千载难逢的夜晚
Di-lat-tat, Di-lat-tat
逐渐膨胀，不断放大
Give me that, give me that bass
给我，给我那低吟
Give me that, give me that ace
给我，给我那招数
My sweet escape with you
亲爱的，我们一起逃离
Let’s go
来吧
Imagine, what words would you say?
想想，你会说什么
If magic was real for today
如过今日的魔法成为现实
I see that you came for the glow
我看见你变得潮红的脸
Want you to know
想让你知晓
That I’m better and brighter with you
我与你一起更灿烂
Woah-oh-oh
喔哦 哦 哦
Come join the moments with perfect view
来加入这瞬的美景
Come find the moments just meant for you
来寻找属于你的时刻
Don’t stop me anymore
不要再阻扰我
So smooth and on a roll
我正在兴头上
Woah-oh, oh, wo-wo-wo-woah-oh
喔哦，哦，喔 喔 喔 喔哦
Ah, Play back, play back...
哈，重播，回放
I’ve got a better feeling
我有更美妙的感受
Ah, Play back, play back...
哈，重播，回放
So take my hand, it’s for you
抓住我的手，它是你的
We could fly and find a way
我们快点想办法
Keep the music on beating, beating
让音乐继续律动，律动
Wo-wo-wo-woah
喔 喔 喔 喔
Stay, stay, stay
继续，逗留，坚持
Wake up and find me you’ll see it
醒来后寻找我，你会明白的
And I’m just tired of finding all meanings
我疲于寻找所有的意义
So I’ll just take us, you won’t need a reason
就让我引导我们，你不需要任何理由
Come taste the flavor, flavor
品尝这鲜美，滋味
Play back, play back
重播，回放